Guide to the Gene Golub Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Gene Golub papers
1950-2007
SC0892
Golub, Gene H. (Gene Howard), 1932-2007
84 Linear feet
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
Description of the Collection
Collection Contents
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2008-045
  Correspondence in box 2-5 = visiting scholars, applicants, general professional, occasional departmental
  - Typescripts for publications of Numerical Analysis Program (NA-91-01 through NA-93-06) followed by Scientific Computing and Computational Mathematics Program (SCCM-93-07 through 94-03); some folders include related correspondence (Box 1)
  - 1 file on Third World Academy of Sciences, 1994 (Box 2)
  - 2 files of lecture transparencies (Optimization and Systems of Nonlinear Equations) (Box 2)
  - Correspondence files (alpha T-Z) 1973-1999 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence files (alpha L-S) 1990-94 (Box 3)
  - 2 files on Thinking Machines Corporation (no correspondence) (Box 3)
  - Correspondence files (Alpha El-K) 1984, 1989-94 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence files (Alpha A-Ei) 1987-94 (Box 5)
  - Golub miscellaneous correspondence 1990-94 (Box 5)
  - Golub research (Box 5)
  - Golub CV file (Box 6)
  - Seminars file (Box 6)
  - Golub correspondence file, misc. unsorted (Box 6)
  - Expenditures reports (Box 6)
  - Published articles by Golub (Box 6)
  - Unsorted, unfoldered typescript papers by others (Box 6)
  - Technical reports from Scientific Computing and Computational Mathematics Program and one from Numerical Analysis Program [not duplicates of those in box 1] (Box 6)
  - Peer review files: correspondence and text of articles reviewed by Golub for publication, 1992-2002 (Box 7)
  - Miscellaneous files on publications (Box 8)
  - Forsythe Fellow Application files (Box 8)
  - CVs [arranged alphabetically, no attached correspondence; not sure if it goes with Forsythe files or not] (Box 8)
  - PhD student files A-R (Box 8)
  - PhD student files S-Z 1993-94 (Box 9)
  - Assorted class files (Box 9)
  - Industrial Affiliates files 1989-95 (Box 9)
  - Proposal & grant files (includes NASA, ARGOSystems, NSF, Army, Navy) 1990s (Box 10)
  - Proposal & grant files (includes ARGOSystems, DOE, NSF) 19902 (Box 11)
  - General grant-info files (Box 11)
  - Several files of slide pages for talks by Golub (Box 11)
  - Proposal & grant files (includes NSF, ARGOSystems) 1990s (Box 12)
  - Files on books by Golub (mostly correspondence with occasional segments of text) 1990s (Box 12)
  - Meeting files, 1994-2004, including SIAM conferences, AAAS meetings, ILAY meetings, and SCI-CADE 95, along with other conferences and appearances (Box 13)
  - SC-CM [Scientific Computing and Computational Mathematics program at SU] administrative files 1987-94 (Box 14)
  - Organizations files 1990-2002: AAAS, NAE, NAS (Box 14)
  - Organizations files: NAS continued (Box 15)
  - SC-CM administrative files 1987-99 (Box 15)
  - Loose materials and unmarked folders (Box 15)
  - Several referee files for articles by others (Box 16)
  - SIAM [Society for Industrial and Applied Mathematics] administrative files 1989-2000 (Box 16)
  - SIAM administrative files, continued (Box 17)
  - Author files A-He: papers submitted for publication by SIAM with related forms and correspondence 1993-97 (Box 17)
  - Author files Hi-T: papers submitted for publication by SIAM with related forms and correspondence 1991-98 (Box 18)
  - Author files V-Z: papers submitted for publication by SIAM with related forms and correspondence 1993-95 (Box 19)
  - Author files, rejected papers A-L 1992-95 (Box 19)
  - Author files, rejected papers M-Z 1992-95 (Box 20)
  - Several master files for SC-CM reports (94-01 – 94-13) (Box 20)
  - Papers by Golub – text and related correspondence pertaining to publication (Box 20)
  - Master files for Numerical Analysis Program technical reports NA 89-01 through -12 and NA 90-01 through -09 (Box 21)
  - RESTRICED BOX: Letters of recommendation and miscellaneous student files (Box 22)
    Restricted 75 years from date of creation.
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2008-159
  - Date book, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Travel Diary, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Transparencies: "Recursive Condition Number Estimation" (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Fitting Ellipses (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Strakoš/Golub (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Golub/Wathen (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - ELM (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Du Brulle (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Cyclic Reduction: History and Recent Developments (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Vorlesungen über numerische Mathematik by Heinz Rutishauser [book] (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Dissertation by Kourosh Modarresi, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Program-1st Dolomites Workshop on Constructive Approximation and Applications, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - NAE Annual & Peer Com. Meetings, October 5-7, 1994, Wash. DC at NAS building (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Contracts, Calendars, Correspondence, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Notebook, Notepad (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - "The skies of the world are filled with electromagnetic waves" [booklet] (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - CME 324 Coursework, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Articles, Correspondence, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Articles, Correspondence, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Articles, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Articles, Correspondence, Leave of Absence Request, Conference Schedule, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Articles, Presentations, Calendars, Itineraries, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Articles, Correspondence, Problems, 1995-2006 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Articles, Correspondence, 1999-2005 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Articles, Correspondence, 1999-2007 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Articles, 2006-2008 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Transparencies: "Matrices, Moments, and Quadrature with applications" (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Student Dissertation Material, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Conference & Seminar Material, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Article: "Semiseparable matrices" (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Look-See File (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Iterative Methods (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Tensor Decomposition (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Iterative – Strakoš (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Saddle-Point (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Seminar (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Genetic/Canonical (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - TLS & LS (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Page Rank (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Articles, Correspondence, Referee Reports, 2003-2005 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Applicant CVs, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Articles, Correspondence, 1988-2005 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Articles, Correspondence, 1998-2005 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Articles, 1984-2004 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Articles, Correspondence, PowerPoint Slides, 1989-2005 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Articles, Correspondence, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - AC Logic (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Backward (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - CS 237A – Numerical Linear Algebra, 2002-2005 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Intrinsic Solutions to the N-dimensional Tensor Equation, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Iterative-Kuznetzov (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Eigenvalue Problems (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Articles, Correspondence, 2001-2005 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Inner/Outer (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - SIAM Journal on Matrix Analysis and Applications, v5 (4), 2004 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Date book, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Regularization (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Perron-Frobenius (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Varimax (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Matrix Computations (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Articles, Correspondence, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Articles, Correspondence, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - CME 324 Coursework, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Saylor (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Oscar Chinellato (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Tropp (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Consulting Agreement (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Problems (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Contracts, Accounts, Contacts, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Photographs (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - CS 339 Coursework, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Articles, Correspondence, 1991-2006 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - CME 302/CS 237A – Notes and Lectures, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Passports & Vaccination Records, 1958-1964 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Articles, Presentations, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Articles, Correspondence, 200-2006 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Summer 2006: Sabbatical at Stanford, 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Notebook (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Guggenheim Fellowship Recipients, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Conference Material, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Conference Material, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Math Workbooks (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Articles, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - LING 001: Introduction to Linguistics - Course Material, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - CME 308: Numerical Linear Algebra - Course Material (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Articles, circa 2004-2007 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Thesis by Diana Maria, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Google/Markov (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - CS 137 Course Material (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - SCCM: Fellowship (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - "Stanford 50" Material, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Accelogic - Consulting Agreement (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Compact Discs (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Interview with Golub (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Problem (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Articles, 1995-2007 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Articles, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Articles, Correspondence, 2006-2007 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Articles, Correspondence, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Articles, Correspondence, 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Matrix Computations (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Mathematics Text (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Mathematics Text (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Problems (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Problems (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - CS 138 Notes (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Dissertation by Yu, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - --Unlabeled (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - NSERC Grant, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Articles, Correspondence, 2002-2006 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Report by J. H. Wilkinson, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Thesis by Young, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Problems, Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - "Afternotes on Numerical Analysis" by Stewart, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Pioneer Day, NCC 1985 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Problems (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Articles, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Stanford Street Names (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Faculty & Resource Guide, School of Engineering, 2004-2005 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Report Cards, 1938-1943 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Bar Mitzvah Certificate, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Commencement Program, Haugan Elementary School, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Certificate of Merit, National High School Art Exhibition (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Commencement Program, High School, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Diploma, B.S., University of Illinois, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Commencement Program, University of Illinois, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Photograph (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Diploma, PhD, University of Illinois, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Alumni Honor Award, University of Illinois, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Pasquini, L., 1994 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Thesis by Young, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Problems (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Problems (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Articles, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Article, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - National Science Foundation Directory, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Articles, Problems (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Articles, Correspondence, Newsletters, 1996-2007 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Articles, Correspondence, Handouts, 2001-2006 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Notebooks (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Articles, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - National Science Foundation Proposal, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - National Science Foundation Proposal, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Articles, Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Articles, Correspondence, 1991-2005 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Knopp File (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - CS 237A (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, clippings, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - CS 135, Winter 1986 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - CS 137A, Spring 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Transparencies: "Numerical Methods for Solving Least Squares Problems with Constraints" (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Deutsch, E. (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Wilkinson Notes (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Lanczos Conference Talk (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Error Bounds for Linear Systems (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Transparencies (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Aut 1987-1988, MSAI [Transparencies] (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Orthogonal Polynomial Talk (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Orthogonal Polynomials (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Numerical Algorithms (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Transparencies: "Quadratic Problems with Constraints" (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Moment Talk (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Quadratic Problems with Constraints Overhead Transparencies (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Golub/Sameh (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Eigenvalue Computations (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Articles, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - "40 Years of Computer Science at Stanford" Symposium, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Andrew Stuart's Course: CS 237A, Autumn 1998 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - CS 237 a, b, c, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - "Numerical Linear Algebra and Data Mining Applications," 2004 (copy 1) (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - "Numerical Linear Algebra and Data Mining Applications," 2004 (copy 2) (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Numerical Solution of Saddle Point Problems (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Orthogonal Polynomials: Computation and Approximation [Draft], 2003 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Scientific Computing G4 An Introduction using MAPLE and MATLAB, 2003 (1 of 2) (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Scientific Computing G4 An Introduction using MAPLE and MATLAB, 2003 (2 of 2) (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Book Lui (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Articles (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Slides – Sung Eun Jo, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Kublanovskaya-Brik (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Elden (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Ahmed Touhami (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Sung-Eun Jo (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Durbin/Watson (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Articles (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - ORSI (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Chu, Moody (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Tanguay (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Boutry (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Zheng-Su (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Friedland (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Eckhardt (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Rump (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Vavasis (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Alter (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Research Grant Information (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Articles, 2003-2006 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Conference on Applied Linear Algebra, Düsseldorf, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Loewner Lectures, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Articles, 1994-2005 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Articles, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - CME 324, CS 199 Coursework, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Articles, Correspondence, 2000-2006 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Committee Related (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Articles, Correspondence, 1971-2006 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Articles (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Articles (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Okawa Foundation Research Grant, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - S.O.R. (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Articles, Correspondence, 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Articles, Correspondence, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Data Mining (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Articles, 1996-2002 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Articles, 1996-2002 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - CS 237A / CS 137A, 1980s-1990s (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - CS 237A, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Journal of Computational Mathematics, 2004-2005 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Chen's Notes – CS 137 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Thesis by Cahill, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Autographed Reprints (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Photographs (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Research Council Policy, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - DOE Proposal: "Advanced Computing….Technology" K. Ko, R. Ryne (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Transparencies: "Solution of Non-Symmetric, Real Positive Linear Systems" (Copy 1) (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Transparencies: "Solution of Non-Symmetric, Real Positive Linear Systems" (Copy 2) (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Transparencies: "Solution of Non-Symmetric, Real Positive Linear Systems" (Copy 3) (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Articles, Correspondence, 1963-2003 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Hong Kong (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Transparencies: "Shape from Moments" (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - "Los Alamos Science," Fall 1982, Summer/Fall 1984 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Photographs (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Notes, Transparencies (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - General Electric Consulting (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Articles, Notes (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Roosevelt High School, Class of June 1949 – 50th Reunion (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Lawrence Berkeley Laboratory Consulting (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Consulting at HP (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Consulting (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Consulting (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Electronics Research Laboratory Memorandum, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - SIAM News, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Universidad Carlos III De Madrid Notebook (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Photographs (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Newsletters, Articles, 1979-1982 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - SIAM / 60th Birthday (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Roosevelt (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - National Science Foundation Proposal, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Articles, Correspondence, 2005-2007 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Clippings (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Problems (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Notes (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Speech (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Name Tag – 3rd EASIAM Conference, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Golub Stationery, Change of Address Form (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Address Books (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - "Fletcher Jones: An American Success Story" [Book] (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Haugan Herald (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Stanford University Postcards (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Awards, Ceremonies (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Passports (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - "Ode to Gene" [Poem] (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - "A Poem for Gene on the Occasion of his 16th Birthday" (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Stanford University First Day Covers (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Photographs (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Photographs – SciCADE (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Oyster card, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Videocassettes:
    - Lincoln, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
    - Father Ted, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
    - Mum's Video, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
    - Scalable Load Balancing by Diffusion, rough sketch, Alan Heirich, 1/6/1993, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
    - Tape 1, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
    - Tape 1, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
    - Tape 2, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
    - Tape 2, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
    - Tape 2, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
    - Tape 3, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
    - Tape 3, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
    - Tape 3, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
    - Workshop in Honor of Gene Golub, Tape 1, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
    - Workshop in Honor of Gene Golub, Tape 2, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
    - Workshop in Honor of Gene Golub, Tape 3, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
    - Workshop in Honor of Gene Golub, Tape 4, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
    - CSci 8899 Computer Science Colloquium "Cyclic Reduction: History, Applications and Extensions," 10/24/1994, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
    - Introduction to Data Parallel Supercomputing, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
    - Gene, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
    - The Best of Visualization, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
    - Nova: Auschwitz (Box 8)
    - Longitude, 7/15/2000 (Box 8)
    - Les Dame de Bois de B, 9/1994; Cold War; I Know Where I'm Going, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
    - British Progs. Oct.-Nov. 1999, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
    - British Progs. Mid-Nov. 1999, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
    - Various TV May/June 1999, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
    - Various July 1999; Prince Philip; Modern Art, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
    - A Diary Between Friends, 3/3/2002, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
    - [Illegible - VHS] (Box 9)
    - Bremner Srebrenica…Nov. 1999, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
    - Golub, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
    - Prof. Jeffrey Sachs, 2001, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 9)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 9)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 9)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 9)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 9)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 9)
    - Wilkinson lecture, 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 9)
    - Portrait of a Marriage, 10/3/1992, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
    - Jefferson in Paris 2:15 Normal Speed; Have I Got News For You; News night April 16, 1999, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
    - Moliere by Mikhail Bulgakov RSC, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
    - Tidbits from "The 8th Parallel Circus," by Anne C. Elster, October 26-27, 1990, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
    - Tales of a City 1-3, 1/11/1994, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
    - Gypsy, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
    - Reagan, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
    - Reagan, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
    - Gene's Birthday Banquet (Box 10)
    - SP Stereo 0-36 mins 50 (Box 10)
    - PAL, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
    - Black Hole Compilation, 1/19/1994, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
    - SVG After Dinner Remarks by Ian Duff, 1/9/04, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
    - 1) London Film 2) American Movies 3) HIGNFY 4) Peter Mandelson, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
    - A Mug's Game, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
    - HIGNFY 7/5; Death of Yugoslavia, 3 hours. 8/5, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
    - Programmes for Gene (to sleep through?, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
    - British progs. (Box 10)
    - 42 Up etc., etc., 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
    - German Scientists in Russia, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
    - 14, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
    - Nixon, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
    - John Paul I, 2 ½ hr., 9/29/1999, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
    - London Progs + House + Hitler + Stalin, Dec. 1999, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
    - David Mamet Movie, Gene's Tape, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
    - The Evolution of Distorted Black Holes, 2/5/1993, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 10)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 10)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 10)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (Betacam) (Box 10)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (Hi-8) (Box 10)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (Hi-8) (Box 10)
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (Hi-8) (Box 10)